Master Thep
My Lord
Where are you going?
I was going to find you in the capital.
What’s happened at home?
Bu- nga
- Bu- nga
- Be careful Thep.
What's wrong with her?
Khem
Tell me What happened?
It was life or death.
Why no telegram?
If I hadn't returned
I’d never have known.
Did you hear me? She tried kill me
You're biased.
You blame her for everything.
And aren't you biased against me?
We'll part ways as I've decided.
Let go of me
Mother
- Duangkhae
- Mother
Let's get engaged.
If I hadn't trusted all of you
I wouldn't be suffering like this.
The fortune teller said...
everything...stems from a curse.
What should we do?
I need to find out...
who cursed my family.
Say that you permit me to enter.
You have permission to enter.
Uncle
What is it?
Do you know her too?
No.
Help
Is anyone there? Help
Master?
Keep this for emergencies.
Protect my wife and child.
Yes sir.
Ah
Something wrong?
Nothing.
I miss you.
Ploy what’s for breakfast?
It smells different.
Good morning Dad.
Morning.
This is so good
Really?
What is it?
Chicken curry with rice.
Let me try some.
It's really good.
Jomthap have some curry.
Okay.
Help yourself.
Good isn't it?
What are you cooking?
Chicken curry with rice.
It's for the Lady to taste.
Anyone who tastes your curry...
will surely fall in love with it.
Where's Mommy?
I saw her go out.
Did she say where to?
We didn't speak.
She isn't answering.
Did you argue yesterday?
No.
But Ploy's been depressed...
since she lost her mother.
I moved my family here
hoping she’d recover
but it hasn't helped.
If we can't find her
in a few hours
we'll file a police report.
In her state of mind
she could be in danger.
I should have installed cameras.
I was so busy with work and renovations
that it slipped my mind.
I'll try calling her as well.
Thank you.
Is it spicy?
Need anything else Jomthap?
Oh.
No.
Aren't you going to eat?
I already ate.
I'll wait outside.
Hello?
Any news on my great- grandfather?
I've searched everywhere
but I can't find the funeral book
for Luang Decha.
No records mention his death either.
We only have Lady Mok’s history...
from her funeral book.
It says she was widowed
after Luang vanished.
Vanished?
Yes.
He disappeared right after
his first wife died.
What about his eldest son?
Thep?
I don't know either.
In that case
we'll never find anything about his family.
I’m afraid so.
I see.
Thank you.
I only found records of Raj
son of Luang and Lady Mok
and your great- grandfather.
To be precise
Luang and Lady Mok
are your great- great- grandparents to you.
Search your house again.
I think the answers
are in that house.
She's a human.
Not a slave.
Not an animal.
You can't just lock her up.
Why not?
Or shall we send her away?
I'm not going back.
I'll wait here for Thep here.
I just remembered I have class.
No time to drop off Chanchao.
Wait.
Nuntan’s class?
Isn't there an exam today?
What's wrong?
Where did she go?
It's hollow inside.
If you want it fixed
we'll need to discuss the details.
Let me think about it.
Sure.
Whoa
Are you okay?
What do you want from me?
You died and forgot everything.
But I'm the only one...
who remembers.
Why am I...
the only one left suffering?
What did I ever do to you?
Look at me.
I said look
Or do I have to gouge your eyes out?
Look me in the eyes.
I said look
Look
You stole Thep from me.
I was there first...
and I had his child.
Look
Come closer.
Are you buying my silence with these?
Is that what you think?
Since you’re about Ploy’s age...
I just wanted your help.
Which ring...
looks best...
for Ploy’s engagement?
This one?
Or...
Cat got your tongue?
Answer the question
What do girls your age like?
It's entirely up to you.
Please excuse me
I have to check on my son.
I left her with Lady Mok.
I don't want to disturb her.
You were a first wife too.
Why can't you understand
someone in my position?
Why...
did you find Thep a new wife?
Your marriage is a wreck
so you hate seeing others happy.
You have to drag them down with you.
So you'll be satisfied?
How dare you
Bu- nga
Should I bring her back and slap her?
No.
If I hadn't promised my son
she wouldn't be acting so smug.
Just you wait.
Once Thep marries Ploy
he'll finally see the truth
and see right from wrong.
I was right all along.
They're tying the knot any day now.
Fool you’ve been tricked again.
I'm sorry.
I’m just so angry for you.
See
They even asked His Highness to preside.
Is this the way of breaking it off?
It's infuriating.
If Luang had let me go
I'd have stopped this.
Two months already.
Look how much you’ve grown.
Your mother’s been feeding you well.
Right?
Did you run away from the wedding?
I...
I wouldn't dare.
Ploy
let's eat
Eat as much as you want now.
Don't worry about fitting into your dress.
You know? Even as a bridesmaid
but I’m still beaming.
So why the long face?
Exactly.
Hey
Even His Highness came here.
You’re so lucky.
I never thought...
his parents would invite him.
Has His Highness left already?
Is something wrong?
He’s presiding over our wedding.
Ploy and I
can't end this as we planned.
You really have to marry another woman...
Bu- nga...
...even though you have a wife and child?
Please listen to me.
I don't want to marry her
but I have no choice.
Then do what you must.
I came all this way
to tell her myself.
I hoped she’d understand.
Bu- nga
(From Somkid Kosaiya)
I've received a letter.
Let me read it to you.
"Dear Bu- nga
I'm so glad
to hear you're doing well
and that the baby
has started rolling over.
She’ll be crawling before we know it.
Actually
I’ve been looking for a house for us
so we can live together in the capital.
But the political situation
is quite worrisome.
It may even lead to bloodshed.
I can't share the details in a letter.
And this...
is why I cannot return home yet.
Please be patient Bu- nga.
With
all my love
Thepparit.
Bloodshed?
He's making up excuses...
because he’s obsessed with his new wife.
They’re all obsessed with the newcomer.
If you don't believe me
come see for yourself.
I think for this spot
I want you...
to design...
a house here. Can you?
Sure this space looks good.
Right.
This side is a bit narrow.
But if...
The reason she...
moved you up here...
was to build a house
for her favorite daughter- in- law.
What's so special about her?
Even if she's of noble descent
she's still beneath her own people.
Plus she's an orphan.
She's not as pretty as you.
Maybe she used black magic
on them both.
If she really went that far
then just let her be.
The wicked will face their karma.
Stay this calm
and you and your child
will end up on the streets.
We have our own magic don't we?
Nora dancers have their spells.
We can't just sit back and take this.
How can I just curse people for no reason?
We don’t know
if they've done anything.
No one can prove that Father.
But she’s taking everything from us.
We're in deep trouble right now.
Our ancestral spells
are not for selfish gain.
Since you chose to be his wife
you must obey him.
If you can't
then walk away.
Don't stay and suffer.
I'm going to the capital.
I need to know...
the truth.
Before you leave do me a favor.
In two days
Father has a doctor's appointment.
Khem keep him away
from the house for a bit.
What's your plan Bu- nga?
Father.
Why must we always pray to our ancestors?
When someone imparts knowledge
and protects you
you show gratitude don’t you?
It's the same with
our Nora ancestral spirits.
If we need something
we just ask them right?
What is it that you want to ask for?
With pure intentions they may grant it.
But remember the spirits
are not for selfish gain.
Master.
I just remembered
the headman wants us to stop by.
He’s got some roasted cashews for us.
Let's go.
Hey
I'm scared
I’m so frightened
Help me
Father
You
You were distracting me
Ancestral spirits
please do not punish her.
She's foolish
and naive.
Please forgive her this one time.
If she has done anything wrong
I will take the blame upon myself.
Is that Lukchan crying?
Yes ma'am.
She's the only baby here.
The other children are all grown.
Where is her mother?
Why leave the baby crying?
Go check on her.
Come on My Lady.
Why are you crying?
Stop it.
Shh. Quiet now.
I don’t even like children.
Stop Stop it
She finally stopped.
I've never seen her up close.
Is she this big already?
She’s about six months old.
So where did her mother go?
She probably went to visit the father.
She asked Lady Mok to look after her.
But she’s gone leaving the baby all alone.
Come.
Let me hold her.
Phon
Why do you want to hold her?
I want a grandchild
not her mother.
Wait for Thep and Ploy’s child.
They’ll be much cuter
You might even get a grandson
It’s been five months
yet no sign of a baby.
Besides I’m fed up with Bu- nga.
Help me think.
What can we do?
Please don't hurt me.
I'm scared.
They were bullying me
I didn't mean to be disrespectful.
Please don't hurt me
They all bullied me... I’m sorry.
Why didn't the spirits curse you
for stealing everything from me?
Why is your life so perfect?
Why aren't you rotting in hell?
I don't know what I did.
If you kill me now
you’ll only add to your karma.
But if you let me go
I will...
make merit for you.
You think merit will help?
Worry about yourself
Hey
Any luck?
Have you found Ploy?
No sign of her.
And...
did you see Inspector Ong?
Yes I did.
He promised to help.
He’s checking the security cameras.
Anyway thank you so much.
You’ve really helped us out.
Come on.
Don't mention it.
By the way
Did a student named Busaban
attend the exam this morning?
A sophomore?
Yeah.
Is there a student named Busaban?
Is she in our major?
Yes I remember her.
She always sits here.
No one ever sits there.
Yes they do.
I've even used this computer.
Professor
that one's been broken since last term.
Are you sure it's this class?
Maybe another major.
Oh hey
Here you are.
I had the registrar's office check.
Our faculty...
has no student named Busaban.
Hello this is Chanchao's father.
Besides me and her Mom
make sure no one else picks her up.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Hey
what's wrong?
I'll tell you later.
Jomthap
Sorry.
I was getting my wounds treated.
Have you found Ploy?
Not yet.
I thought you were home.
Did Busaban go to your house?
Why?
Is something wrong?
Then be careful.
- She might be armed.
- Okay.
I'm heading home now.
I'll check when I arrive.
Alright.
You’ve kept what’s mine
for too long.
What do you want from me?
Your life.
Fine.
I can't do anything to you right now.
If I die like this
I’ll return as a ghost just like you.
Then we can fight on equal terms.
And you will know
just how agonizing
my suffering has been.
Leave the baby.
Take this and find a man you deserve.
If that's what Thep really wants
I will leave.
I won't take a single cent.
Bu- nga
How's Father?
Go check on him.
Give me your baby.
Why do you want her?
Someone wants her.
Die
Bu- nga
Run
My baby My baby
Bu- nga don't
I got the CCTV footage.
You were talking to someone
who isn't there.
The person you met
isn't a scammer.
In fact...
she isn't even human.
You're finally here.
The problem you're facing
the police can't help you with this.
This necklace will protect you.
We found Mom.
Mommy
Ploy